some of y'all should stick to just working for white people that you can talk about at the
at the water cooler because you really ain't cut like you don't have the range to work with folks
that you're going to actually have to give a fuck about you know just be real with yourself and stop
wasting our time you know we talked about corporations and these shitty corporations
and how terrible they treat the people that work for them right and um you know then you get folks
that are like i don't want to work for a corporation like i want to work for you know a small business
or i want to work for somebody that's like really about it and you know doing something and then you
do but here's the thing that i want to remind everybody when you work for a small business
nine times out of ten you are dealing directly with the person who is signing your checks
it is a different interaction your work has a different value right because there's only so
many people that are going to be able to be at that job so you're very valuable there um but also when
you're interacting with that person directly that there's not going to be that nebulous lack of
accountability that you have when you're part of a massive staff and i have noticed that more people
than i'm really thought really they can't handle that they do not like and they cannot manage and
they cannot handle the actual boss being like hey what is this or hey this needs to be corrected
or hey why didn't you xyz they want the actual ability to be just kind of like a number
so just something to keep in mind because i am a small business and i end up you know working
with people and hiring people and the amount of times that i've had people on my staff who
simply do not follow through or think that you know their their role is just like a casual thing
that they can just like you know when they feel like it or when something you know comes up etc is
bonkers no this is a team a real one not just a fake one
you